http://www.jerrybaker.com/privacy-policy

Cola refreshes--both you and your yard
Quit itchin' to pitch out old panty hose!
Duct tape...in the GARDEN? Yes!
Save those chops to help your crops!
Don't hold your breath--these tricks will lick the hics!
Luxurious locks... fresh from the garden
This oil thinks outside the kitchen
Cool it...with cucumbers
Say "NO!" to B.O.
Chalk these ideas up to old-fashioned ingenuity!
The whole ball of wax: 5 wacky uses for wax paper
5 easy reasons to reach for fabric softener sheets
Furious at fruit flies? Flatten 'em fast!
Don't toss that tube--make it work!
About Jerry
Our Mission
Jerry's Blog
Buy Two Get One FREE!
Continue Shopping
Checkout »
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Introduction
Thank you for visiting this website. We recognize and respect the importance of maintaining the privacy of our customers. This Privacy Policy details what information we collect, as well as why we collect it, what we do with it, and how we keep that information secure. This Privacy Policy is part of our Terms of Use, which governs your use of this website.
Why We Gather Information
We strive to provide our customers with excellent products and customer service. We collect personally identifiable information (PII) to allow us to process transactions more efficiently, enhance the shopping experience, notify about special offers and discounts, and provide the best customer service possible.
What We Collect
We collect PII from you when you visit our website and through e-mail. We also collect PII during transactions, sponsored events, content viewing, and contests/sweepstakes. PII includes your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone and cell phone numbers, wireless service provider, and all other information that identifies you.
We may collect information about your interaction with this site. For example, we may use website analytics tools on our site to retrieve information from your browser, including the site you came from, the search engine(s) and the keywords you used to find our site, the pages you view within our site, your browser add-ons, and your browser's width and height. We may also use technologies, such as cookies and web beacons (described below), to collect information about the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take on our site. Additionally, we may collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring website addresses.
When you receive newsletters or promotional e-mail from us, we may use web beacons (described below), customized links or similar technologies to determine whether the e-mail has been opened and which links you click in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or other information. We may also supplement the information we collect with information obtained from other companies.
We maintain your PII, along with a record of purchases, in a secure database. The only people with access to that information are the employees necessary to process customer service functions.
It's important to remember that when you put PII online in a way that can be viewed by third parties (i.e., through e-mail, message boards, and chat areas), those same parties may collect your data. We are not responsible for the actions of third parties in collecting your PII.
We do our very best to keep PII safe. But there may be times when inadvertent disclosure occurs, and we therefore cannot guarantee that PII will never be shared. An example of this is if a third party misrepresents him or herself as someone we would share our information with, and we disclose information in full compliance with this Privacy Policy.
We also gather information about how visitors navigate around this website by using data collected from "cookies" and "web beacons." This information helps us improve the user experience and the overall quality of our products and services.
How We Use Cookies and Web Beacons
In order to provide better service when you return to our site, we may use Cookies and Web Beacons to store your preferences and information about such things as items added to your shopping cart, purchases you have made with us, what pages you visit, and past activity at a site. We may also employ Web Beacons from third parties in order to help us compile aggregated statistics regarding the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns or other operations of our site.
"Cookies" are tiny pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are also used to ensure that you are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads and to customize webpage content based on your browser type (Firefox or Microsoft Explorer, for example). Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. Web Beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs or clear gifs - are used to assist in delivering cookies on our site and allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We may include Web Beacons in promotional e-mail messages or our newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.
If you want to disable cookies, there is a simple procedure in most Internet browsers that allows you to turn off cookies. Please remember, however, that cookies may be required to allow you to use certain features of our site.
If you prefer not to accept cookies on your computer, we invite you to place your order with one of our Customer Service representatives by calling toll-free 1-800-888-0010 during regular workday business hours (Monday - Friday, 9:00 a.m. - 5:00 p.m. EST).
How We Use Your Information
We want to provide the best possible customer experience. In order to do this, we collect personally identifiable information that allows us to:
Process, track, and follow up on orders
Provide the services requested
Send occasional mail and email offers about products, upcoming sales, and other promotions that may be of interest to you
Send e-mail newsletters, if requested
Improve our product selection and customer service
We may contact you about special updates concerning this website, services, and policies. We may also contact you to verify new user information or to fulfill a customer service request.
We may combine the personally identifiable information we receive online and offline with outside records and other information about you, your computer, and/or devices that we obtain from other companies and sources, including third-party data suppliers and public databases. We may use that information to enhance our ability to market products and services that may be of interest to you.
We make certain PII and other information available to third parties to assist us with marketing campaigns and provide products and service to our customers. We also share this information with third parties who help us produce, deliver, bill, collect payments and otherwise manage, market, fulfill orders and perform customer service related functions and data or information technology related services. These companies are obligated to protect the information they receive.
We may also disclose certain PII and other information to third parties whose practices are not governed by this Privacy Policy. They may contact you via postal or email to present products or services that may be of interest to you. To request that your PII and other information not be shared with these third parties, click here.
If you need to change any of your personally identifiable information at any time, you may do so by clicking here, or by contacting our Customer Service Department by:
Calling toll-free: 1-800-336-5885 Via e-mail: customerservice@jerrybaker.com
Consent
By using this site and our products and services, you consent to our collection of PII. When you register for an account, purchase a product or service, communicate with us, or use this site, you consent to our collection of the PII in accordance with this policy that you disclose or make available to us during those activities.
By providing PII and other information to us, you consent to our sharing your information with others as described above. You also understand that, not withstanding the other policy provisions herein, you cannot opt-out of having your information shared with the third parties who assist us in producing, delivering, billing, collecting payments and otherwise managing, marketing, fulfilling orders and who perform customer service related functions and data or information technology related services.
Children's Privacy Statement
Our site is not intended to be used by children under the age of 13. We do not collect any personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 knowingly, and we do not use any information that has been inadvertently collected. If we learn that we have collected information from someone under the age of 13, we immediately delete it from our database. Please note that children should always receive parental permission before sharing any information online with any website.
How to Opt Out of Mailings
If you do not wish to receive offline offers from us, or are not interested in having your personally identifiable information shared with third parties or receiving special offers from them, please click here.
You may also mail your request to the attention of "Opt Out/Customer Service" at:
Customer Service P.O. Box 930006 Dept. 20Wixom, MI 48393
Or you can contact us via email at customerservice@jerrybaker.com.
If you no longer wish to receive e-mail messages from us, you may use the link that appears at the bottom of each of our promotional e-mails to unsubscribe, or click here.
All requests to be removed from our mailing or e-mailing lists will be addressed as quickly as possible, and in the case of e-mail newsletters, in no more than 7 days. Please keep in mind that your request may overlap a current mailing. Should this happen, we apologize for any temporary inconvenience it may cause you.
If you want to stop receiving unwanted mailings from any company, you can register with national clearinghouse organizations or governmental groups. The biggest and most widely used is the Direct Marketing Association (DMA). The DMA website provides mail, e-mail, and telemarketing contacts. To learn more, visit its website@ the-dma.org, or call the organization at (202) 955-5030.
Your California Privacy Rights: Notice to California Customers
California's "Shine the Light" law, Civil Code section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California customers asking about the businesses' practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. Alternately, such businesses may have in place a policy not to disclose personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option to opt-out of such information-sharing. As discussed above, if you wish to opt-out of our sharing of your personal information with third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes offline, please click here, or for e-mail, please click here. While this notice is designed to comply with California's "Shine the Light" law, the opt-out option is also available to all our users. To find out more about your opt-out rights, please contact us via e-mail or postal address described below.
Disclosure of Information
We may disclose any personally identifiable information when we believe disclosure to be appropriate (i) to comply with any law, regulation, governmental request, or judicial process; (ii) if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate this website; or (iii) to protect the rights or property of Baker's Best Health, its users, sponsors, providers, licensors, and/or merchants.
We always welcome your questions and feedback. For privacy-related issues, including information about disclosure of personally identifiable information, please contact us at:
Customer Service P.O. Box 930006 Dept. 20Wixom, MI 48393 Toll-free: 1-800-720-0099 Email: customerservice@jerrybaker.com
Our Security Commitment
We have put into place appropriate procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain security and properly use the information that we collect. No procedures or systems, however, can be completely secure, so we do not guarantee that unauthorized disclosures and/or access will not happen.
The Right to Amend This Policy
The Internet is always changing, which means our Privacy Policy can change at any time. Whenever we update our policy, the revised Notice will be posted to this page. As soon as we post the Notice, the new policy will go into effect. If you continue to use our website after the Notice has been posted, then you'll be accepting the Privacy Policy as written.
Last Updated: June 10, 2016
Sign up for ourFREE E-Newsletter!
Enter Email
Save 25%on your next order
This site uses cookies to collect data. By continuing to browse, you accept our
Privacy Policy.
Agree
Sign up for SPECIAL OFFERS
Sign up to receive emails and get 25% OFF your first order!
Email address
Sign Up
